Twelve is the new eleven.
Ocean's Twelve is a thriller, crime film directed by Steven Soderbergh.
Despite pulling off one of the biggest heists in Las Vegas history and splitting the $160 million take, each
of the infamous Ocean's crew have tried to go straight, lay low and live a legit life ...
but that's proven to be a challenge.
Casino owner Terry Benedict demands that Danny Ocean return
the money, plus millions more in interest.
Unable to come up the cash, the crew is forced to come together to pull off another series of heists,
this time in Rome, Paris, and Amsterdam – but a Europol agent is hot on their heels.
Danny Ocean, played by George Clooney.
Tess Ocean, played by Julia Roberts.
Rusty Ryan, played by Brad Pitt.
Linus Caldwell, played by Matt Damon.
Isabel Lahiri, played by Catherine Zeta-Jones.
Terry Benedict, played by Andy Garcia.
Ocean's Twelve is a 2004 American heist comedy film directed by
Steven Soderbergh and written by George Nolfi.
The second installment in the Ocean's film trilogy franchise and the sequel to Ocean's Eleven (2001), the film features an ensemble cast including George Clooney, Brad Pitt, Matt
Damon, Catherine Zeta-Jones, Andy García, Don Cheadle, Bernie Mac, Julia Roberts, Casey Affleck, Scott Caan, Vincent Cassel, Eddie Jemison, Carl Reiner, and Elliott Gould.
Ocean's Twelve was released theatrically in the United
States on December 10, 2004, by Warner Bros.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $362.9 million
worldwide, becoming the tenth-highest-grossing film of 2004.
It was followed by Ocean's Thirteen (2007), with
Soderbergh and most of the cast again returning.
The film explores themes of paris, france, rome, italy,
amsterdam, netherlands, competition, ex-girlfriend.
The tone is intense.